edgebee.com 2018-03-12

# Edgebee - Privacy policy

**Privacy Policy**

Our Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect and use the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site and our services.

**What Information Do We Collect?**

When you visit Edgebee.com (our "Web site") you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and Web site use information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse our Web site. 

**Personal Information You Choose to Provide.**

**Registration Information.**

At this time we do not require any personal information for a user to play one of Edgebee.com’s games. 

You must provide us with your email address if you choose to register to create an account on our Web site, and provide personal information to PayPal when purchasing Site Tokens. 

When confirming that a purchase of Site Tokens was processed and that payment has indeed been received, PayPal communicates to us your name and the email address you registered with PayPal. 

If you are less than 14 years of age and you wish to create an account, a parent must create an account for you and provide their email address. Registration by a child under the age of 14 is considered evidence of parental consent, and the email provided to be the email of the parent. 

You must be 18 years and older to purchase Site Tokens on Edgebee.com, whether for yourself or as guardian to a child using our Web site. The receipt of payment is considered actual, verifiable consent from the parent to the child's use of our website and to any information that was divulged as reasonably necessary to process payments, verify and maintain the account. 

**Email Information.**

If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses. 

  2. **Web Site Use Information**

Similar to other commercial Web sites, Edgebee.com utilizes a standard technology called "cookies" (see explanation below, "What Are Cookies?") and Web server logs to collect information about how our Web site is used. Information gathered through cookies and Web server logs may include the date and time of visits, time spent at our Web site and its games and the Web sites visited just before and just after our Web site. We, our advertisers and ad serving companies may also use small technology or pieces of code to determine which advertisements and promotions users have seen and how users responded to them. 

We use Google as one of our advertisers. Google uses the DART cookie to enable it to serve ads to you based on your visits to this site and other sites on the Internet. If you want to opt out of the use of the DART cookie please visit Google's site at <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>. 

**How Do We Use the Information That You Provide to Us?**

Broadly speaking, we use personal information for purposes of administering and expanding our business activities, providing customer service and making available other products and services to our customers and prospective customers. Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our Web site, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. You may notify us at any time if you do not wish to receive these offers by updating your user profile on the Web site. 

**What Are Cookies?**

A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a Web site, that site's computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically designated for cookies. Each Web site can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser's preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a Web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites. Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies that originate from their sites. We have no access or control over those cookies. 

**How Do We Use Information We Collect from Cookies?**

As you use our Web site, the site uses its cookies to differentiate you from other users. In some cases, we also use cookies to prevent you from seeing unnecessary advertisements or requiring you to log in more than is necessary for security. Cookies, in conjunction with our Web server's log files, allow us to calculate the aggregate number of people visiting our Web site and which parts of the site are most popular. This helps us gather feedback in order to constantly improve our Web site and better serve our customers. Cookies do not allow us to gather any personal information about you and we do not generally store any personal information that you provided to us in your cookies. 

**Sharing Information with Third Parties**

We will not share your information with third parties unless otherwise disclosed in this Policy (for example statistical data about web site use for advertisers). We may disclose your information to those that help us provide technical, administrative and data processing services (including hosting, billing, fulfillment, and data storage and security) "Affiliated Parties".  The Affiliated Parties to whom we disclose your personal information all have agreed to abide by this Privacy Policy. Please note that some of these Affiliated Parties have separate privacy policies that govern their collection, use and storage of information that you provide to them directly. Example: Paypal has its own privacy policy for customers using its services. 

We may transfer all of your personal information to a third party in the case of a merger or acquisition of Edgebee.com and our business by a third party. 

**Notice of New Services and Changes**

Occasionally, we may use the information we collect, including your email, to notify you about important changes to our Web site, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. As our customer, you will be given the opportunity to notify us of your desire not to receive these offers by updating your user profile on the Web site. 

**How Can You Access and Correct Your Information?**

You may request access to all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain in our database by emailing . 

**Certain Disclosures**

We may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the law or comply with legal process served on us or affiliated parties; (b) protect and defend our rights and property, our site, the users of our site, and/or our affiliated parties; (c) act under circumstances to protect the safety of users of our site, us, or third parties. 

**What About Other Web Sites Linked to Our Web Site?**

We are not responsible for the practices employed by Web sites linked to or from our Web site nor the information or content contained therein. Often links to other Web sites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of our Web site. 

Please remember that when you use a link to go from our Web site to another Web site, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other Web site, including Web sites which have a link on our Web site, is subject to that Web site's own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding. 

**Your Consent**

By using our Web site you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. You also consent to this Privacy Policy being in the English language. If we change our privacy policies and procedures, we will post those changes on our Web site to keep you aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it.
